<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>📄Research on Jask&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://jask.cc/en/posts/research/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 📄Research on Jask&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 20:35:23 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jask.cc/en/posts/research/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Multi AI-Model Discuss</title>
      <link>https://jask.cc/en/posts/research/multi-aimodel-discuss/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 20:35:23 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jask.cc/en/posts/research/multi-aimodel-discuss/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;tldr&#34;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For now, many company develop their own AI-Model. But they all vary in quality, and I collected answers from different AI models on the same topic. I can&amp;rsquo;t determine which model is more accurate. Topic is &amp;ldquo;Study which burns more calories, running three kilometers fast (average pace 5 min 45 sec/KM) or jogging three kilometers (average pace 7 min/KM)? Now ai era, the hottest is big data + AI and blockchain + AI, the market has appeared a lot of use cases, but when we all know that there is a focus in the line of sight, then there is a blind spot, people are concerned about the artificial intelligence, then, there are those non-artificial intelligence industry is in the next five years is promising?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Blockchain Market Research Report Q1 Q3 2025</title>
      <link>https://jask.cc/en/posts/research/blockchain-market-research-report-q1-q3-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2024 20:00:56 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jask.cc/en/posts/research/blockchain-market-research-report-q1-q3-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;blockchain-industry-financing-and-market-dynamics-research-report-2024&#34;&gt;Blockchain Industry Financing and Market Dynamics Research Report 2024&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;i-report-overview&#34;&gt;I. Report Overview&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2024 was a year of rapid growth and adjustment in the blockchain industry, with the financing market evolving in response to technological innovations, market price volatility, and changes in the macroeconomic environment. Bitcoin and ethereum reached all-time highs in March 2024, followed by dramatic market volatility. Against this backdrop, venture capital (VC) financing activities also exhibit a unique rhythm, demonstrating the lag effect between market sentiment and investment decisions. By analyzing the financing data and quarterly performance of different sectors, it is possible to reveal the investment trends, technological advances, and future development potential of the blockchain industry.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
